# **Advertisement**

## Full-Time PHP Developer for startup in Brno

To support the development of our internal startup we are looking for a full-time PHP developer to support our team in Brno.

## What we're looking for

We're looking for someone who meets the following criteria:

- 1. 3 or more years experience with PHP, familiar with modern design patterns
- 2. 3 or more years experience with \*SQL databases
- 3. familiar with Git
- 4. eager to learn and willing to take responsibility
- 5. experience with designing and discussing application architecture
- 6. able to communicate in English

## Our technology stack

Our stack consists of the following technologies. Having experience with them is considered a big plus.

- 1. MariaDB Galera cluster with 6 nodes in 3 datacenters across Europe
- 2. RabbitMQ
- 3. Nette and Symfony PHP frameworks (we use parts of both)
- 4. Ansible for provisioning
- 5. Supervisord for daemon management
- 6. CentOS Linux (RHEL family)

#### Our workflow

We care a lot about our workflow and always aim to run things as efficiently as possible.

- 1. Scrum with 2-week sprints
- 2. GitHub for repository hosting, communication and Scrum board
- 3. Code reviews as part of our Definition of Done
- 4. Continuous Integration with automated tests (Nette Tester) and automatic deployments
- 5. HipChat for team communication

#### Interested?

Did we pique your interest? Send us an e-mail (jobs@dotblue.net) detailing your experience and we'll get back to you as soon as possible. Make sure to include links to your Github, Stack Overflow and similar profiles, source code samples, or anything else that you think might be of interest to us.

# **Curriculum Vitae**

#### Personal information

#### Martin Zlámal

Brnířov 118, 345 06 Kdyně (Czech Republic)

Phone: +420 723 764 899 Email: mrtnzlml@gmail.com

Web: www.zlml.cz

in LinkedIn: cz.linkedin.com/in/mrtnzlml

## Work experience

**ANT studio s.r.o.** (May 2015 – to present)

Development of internal website application, the primary focus on Nette Framework.

**FRESH-Hosting.cz** (2013 – to present)

Development of website appliaction (using Nette Framework), webhosting infrastructure and clients services.

**Orgis IT** (2013 – May 2015)

Development of website appliactions (using Nette Framework) and Enterprise Resource Planning systems.

**Advisor of Endora company** (October 2011 – January 2013)

Technical support, extending of clients services.

## Education, training and courses

University of West Bohemia – Faculty of Electrical Engineering (2015 – to present), Environmental engineering, Masters's degree (actual)

University of West Bohemia – Faculty of Electrical Engineering (2013 – 2015), Environmental engineering, Bachelor's degree (successfully finished)

Mastering Nette (October 2014) – got certificate

Web appliaction development using Nette Framework (November 2012) – got certificate

#### Lectures and articles

Doctrine for non-doctrine programmers (25. April 2015) – czech only

Barák budoucnosti (28. March 2015) – czech only

Nette Framework 2.3-dev (10. December 2014) – czech only

Node.js – JavaScript on the server (3. December 2014) – czech only

From Caesara to the QR code (12. April 2014) – czech only

Nette Framework 2.1-dev (18. December 2013) – czech only

66 technical articles on personal website (valid at 25. October 2015) – mostly czech

#### Personal skills

I have good communication skills thanks to public presentations during my work at Orgis IT and ANT studio s.r.o. I also have good experience with project leading thanks to Orgis IT and FRESH-Hosting project. I know very well PHP, Nette Framework (which is my primary specialization), database systems (MySQL, Redis), HTML/xHTML, CSS/JavaScript. I am also familiar with GNU/Linux (daily user).

## **Cover Letter**

Dear Mr. Dobeš,

I would like to apply for the position of PHP Developer for startup in Brno. I read about this position at forum.nette.org.

You can find my CV in the attachment. As you can see I am familiar with the PHP itself, especially witch the Nette Framework which is my primary specialization. I visited two intense Nette courses and gained two certificates. But I am not focused on obtaining certificates rather than knowledge. That's why I am playing around with this framework for more than five years.

I am also interested in modern technologies you mentioned in advertisement. To be completely honest I don't know Ansible and Supervisord very well but I am eager to learn about it. But otherwise I fulfil all of the requirements, especially Git knowledge. I know Git as a regular user as well as it's technical background.

Why I want to apply? I want to do cool stuff. I like challenging job. And that's not what I am getting in my current job. Now it's more repetitive than challenging. I am also very interested in new startups, because there is always a lot of open minded people. It's very inspirative.

As you mention at the very end of the advertisement, here si my Github profile (github.com/mrtnzlml). I also want to share with you my blog (zlml.cz) because this is the place where I am presenting all of my work results for more than three years now. I hope it will be somehow interesting for you and that it will show you my knowledge. I believe this is much more better than CV.

You can contact me directly by telephone 123 456 789 or you can call my previous employer (987 654 321).

I will be available for employment after my contract ends. It will be at the end of next month. But we can meet sooner so I can learn more about this job and you can better know me.

Thank you for your time.

Sincerely yours,

Martin Zlámal